in the weather, james might be last week it
天气，詹姆斯可能是上周了
Group
组
sascha müller the german aerospace
萨莎·米勒德国航空航天
enterprise dae wants to be about the elven
企业敢于想成为精灵
pc and target from pain to best practice
pc和目标，从痛苦到最佳实践
in their electrical problems and
他们的电问题和
Solutions europe gets well on the train rating
欧洲解决方案在火车等级上表现良好
infrastructure for our project to des
我们设计项目的基础设施
turning agenda wants to be looking like the
议事日程看起来像
first of all the way we look in holyhead
首先，我们看着圣头
structured products for dz from the end of July
dz的结构化产品从7月底开始
the casting area how to be set up
铸造区域如何设置
pikes in maiden and vodka cockpit vc and
在少女和伏特加座舱vc和
new configuration options to set the
新的配置选项来设置
world final look at what they can set up
世界最终看他们可以设置什么
in particles like walking advocacy twitter
在像步行倡导这样的粒子中
and just one world one project project
还有一个世界一项目
manager developed
经理发展
the penaltys using it repositories and
使用它的存储库的罚款和
finally after we have done to set up
终于在我们完成设置之后
where we can set up the project in
我们可以在其中建立项目的地方
the picture fits roger reddig okay so
图片适合roger reddig好的，所以
get here is taiko and may the witch
到达这里是太鼓，愿女巫
ernstings on-site infrastructure day
恩斯特斯汀现场基础设施日
private car matte mayor testing
私家车哑光市长测试
and integrate world of the cribs
并整合婴儿床的世界
technologies but the questions
技术，但问题
main problem set up system works and of
主要问题建立系统的工作原理
course 11
路线11
[Music]
[音乐]
It is not one on the way to the top
它不是通往巅峰之路的人
jobs
就业
because we all have very different nice
因为我们每个人都有很大不同
that's ok go on some compilation of
没关系，继续整理
answers of the workers and the context of
工人的回答和背景
project are using it infrastructure for
项目正在将其用于基础架构
the largest unit and remain i
最大的单位，并保持我
work on is called the satellite which is
正在工作的被称为卫星
great place to work for developing model
开发模型的好地方
based systems engineering applications
基于系统工程的应用
to make it simple by modeling and
通过建模使其变得简单
developing applications models of
开发以下应用程序模型
project based research focus money
基于项目的研究重点资金
projects for students as well
学生项目
master studies july is about project
7月硕士课程是关于项目的
which is not the wall project
这不是墙项目
that can independent research
可以独立研究
because as well as products project manager
因为以及产品项目经理
engineers heart and this difference
工程师的心和这种差异
june fortis projects and meet with the
六月富通项目，并与
weary head of project project which
疲倦的项目负责人
contains
包含
Often new wave a setup will be masters at
通常，新的设置将是掌握
the top level in more clean tech world
清洁技术世界中的最高水平
to the holidays platform which wants
到想要的假期平台
The penaltys collected from the
从
is harry to define the product for
竭力为以下产品定义产品
application and used look at one of our
应用程序和二手看看我们之一
plugins like can just add water
像插件一样可以加水
masterplan thats a better plugins
总体规划，那就是更好的插件
look like you think project
看起来像您认为的项目
heiko weber and setup hughes inc
Heiko Weber和Setup Hughes Inc
tyco answer is herbs for plugins fdp
tyco的答案是插件fdp的草药
some of them but some of you
其中一些，但你们中的一些
may need some nice configuration as well
可能还需要一些不错的配置
[Music]
[音乐]
Configuration of a complex supply chain
配置复杂的供应链
jenkins show of the entertainer
詹金斯表演的艺人
because they are freezing cold then like on the
因为他们是冰冷的，然后像
set up amount platform as if it had
设置金额平台，就好像它有
the tourist you are the temporary me
游客是你的临时工
think you have to come the user
认为您必须要吸引用户
experience with music project the witch
音乐项目巫婆的经验
project director scott
项目总监斯科特
can use the second way of getting the
可以使用第二种方式
seas in a picture like canon oslo the
海洋像佳能奥斯陆
enemies pose tories we can just say okay
敌人假装保守党，我们可以说好
just get your plugins from this update
只需从此更新中获取您的插件
Time discovered the panz is by profession
时间发现潘兹是职业
at least that's what they do
至少那是他们所做的
used for developing the basic i just a
用于开发基本的我只是一个
game features trumpet repositories
游戏功能小号存储库
without having annie and sourcecode
没有安妮和源代码
continue because of moment in the word of having
继续因为有
to maintain the day's platform as well
维持当天的平台
car and testing and what are you watching
汽车和测试，您在看什么
set the property of the day to set up
设置当天要设置的属性
then put on bradley manning in
然后穿上布拉德利·曼宁
hettersroth and there are star
hettersroth，还有星星
cooperation on the time we can take
我们可以花时间合作
something i said i continue ding is the
我说我继续听的东西是
first test video often ends with handle and
第一个测试视频的结尾通常是
jenkins level
詹金斯水平
we want the playoffs the wave ii of
我们想要季后赛的第二波
Monaco again and stop the ex
摩纳哥再次停止前
terrorist lot of time they can dance the
恐怖的很多时间，他们可以跳舞
skin lux and jenkins when the outside
外时皮肤勒克斯和詹金斯
jacko code coverage of the training camp
训练营的Jacko代码覆盖率
last update november in new project
11月新项目中的最新更新
update manager updating the big bottles
更新经理更新大瓶子
to have
有
[Music]
[音乐]
an update of the manager plugins simple
简单更新管理器插件
execution only the numbers for search of
仅执行要搜索的数字
it was very important thing that we had
这是非常重要的事情
with external the penaltys be made in
与外部的罚款
some cases you get the following
在某些情况下，您得到以下信息
fact start-up days platform james ensor
事实启动日平台james ensor
loading connection brakes and we
加载连接制动器，我们
eliminate as well as 42 important to tackle
消除以及解决42个重要问题
repository moersdorf in the news the
新闻中的Moersdorf仓库
penaltys in the days platform of all
所有天平台的罚款
wasting light of time so discovery basic
浪费时间，所以发现很基础
picture set up with you would like to get
您想要获得的图片设置
you into the case that we do not want you
您进入我们不希望您的情况
just one project but actually series of
只是一个项目，但实际上是一系列
projects records private customers series
项目记录私人客户系列
project i can not be different now
项目我现在不能不同
Law of project project project be
工程项目法则
required artifex of project repositories
项目存储库的必需术语
[Music]
[音乐]
jenkins takes the necessary artifex
詹金斯采取必要的Artifex
ducks fists here in an interview
鸭子拳头在这里接受采访
repository of widge act the old
寡妇库
project can dance factory features
项目可以舞蹈工厂特色
display continue the cherry long to get
显示继续樱桃久了
our dependence project basica you in the
我们的依赖项目使您在
tank platform never wants to reference it
坦克平台永远不想引用它
it the touri posse torri
它是toruri posse torri
laura defect if you in the we
劳拉缺陷，如果你在我们
discovered one way to the sausage
发现了香肠的一种方法
fear would have to be very young
恐惧一定要很小
development board and what i fire to day
开发板和我今天要烧的东西
time and what ever you make me picture
时间和你让我生动的照片
One day's platform is on the roll
一日平台上线了
in fact or maybe i'm off to update the
实际上或者也许我要更新
[Music]
[音乐]
candidate for justice projects
司法项目候选人
talking about having the just one
谈论只有一个
screen and jenkins as well as basica
屏幕和詹金斯以及basica
directly is worked for one with brunch
直接为早午餐工作
basic we actually heart shape car industry
基本我们实际上是心脏形状的汽车行业
studios bit of context here is how we
工作室的上下文是我们的方式
have set up it's based on summit project
已经根据峰会项目进行了设置
development braunschweig
不伦瑞克发展
most of the work and it's time to
大部分的工作，现在该
major release again under integration
整合后再次发布主要版本
bvi duo manual testing and keep our
bvi duo手动测试并保留我们的
separated close said fred from jupiter
与木星分开说弗雷德
development because then if the
发展，因为如果
testing and bugfixing poetry can just
测试和错误修正诗歌可以
the master and development for
掌握和发展
difference is that remains different
区别在于仍然不同
ways to configure jobs for example and
配置作业的方法，例如和
master wants to build by mac developer
大师想要由Mac开发人员构建
and the jobs are just come and go away
工作就随波逐流
we can have many of them is the
我们可以有很多是
question is not an original example here
问题不是这里的原始示例
passwords displays property and get
密码显示属性并获取
some great feedback like project example
一些很棒的反馈，例如项目示例
jobs basic resources target for the
工作的基本资源目标
Station's crew to be over is up to date
车站的工作人员最新
The penaltys ends up waste resort picture
罚款最终浪费了度假胜地的照片
as well as on development board and avery
以及开发委员会和avery
finish the picture donate the jobs
完成图片捐赠工作
should the theory of the overall choir losses
合唱团整体损失的理论应该
development picture-interview the project
开发图片采访项目
development develops download shop
开发开发下载商店
basic edition feature like desktop widget
基本版功能，例如桌面小部件
[Music]
[音乐]
development of the new features and
新功能的开发和
projects
项目
prince williams and take that i the
威廉王子，并认为我
releases from the differential is july in
从差异发布7月
Arabidopsis exercises again and if
拟南芥再次运动，如果
the zdh can refinery setup new project
zdh可以炼油厂设置新项目
and infrastructure jessica woodworth
和基础设施杰西卡·伍德沃思（Jessica Woodworth）
then it's like yeast template project
那就像酵母模板项目
project to set up artist to some of the
设立艺术家的项目
project the guy copyshops project
盖伊专卖店项目
and logistics
和物流
so know
这样知道
[Applause]
[鼓掌]
who a bruise
谁擦伤
[Music]
[音乐]
July
七月
problems with one pc will be with the
一台电脑的问题将与
guest side as you will be petersburgs
客人，因为你将是彼得斯堡
force india or chat thinks that is
印度力量或聊天认为
except the enemy lightbody viewing with
除了敌人的光体与
crapware the interstate so my
废话我的州际公路
objects of rostocker kontrons average
罗斯托克·控创平均目标
dji.dji feedback is there because of a
dji.dji反馈之所以存在是因为
to recognize virus
识别病毒
Then I would like to think about it
那我想想一下
[Applause]
[鼓掌]